<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bugs &amp; Beetles</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to\nBugs and Beetles</string>

    <string name="black_swallowtail">Black Swallowtail: The caterpillar is usually found eating parsley and carrot tops.
        The butterfly is large, quite beautiful, and a good pollinator.</string>

    <string name="ladybug">Lady Bug: A beneficial insect that feeds on aphids, mealybugs mites, and soft-bodied
        insects.  200-500 aphids can be consumed during the larval stage.</string>

    <string name="monarch_butterfly">Monarch Butterfly: Eggs are laid on milkweed plants and the caterpillar eats these
        exclusively.  The milkweed makes the caterpillar unpalatable to predators.  If there
        are no milkweed plants, there are no monarchs.</string>

    <string name="squash_bug">Squash Bug: Adults and nymphs suck sap from the leaves and stems of all  cucurbits,
        especially squash and pumpkins.  Damage symptoms include the wilting of plant
        leaves.</string>


    <string name="asian_longhorn">Asian Longhorned Beetle: An invasive species extremely dangerous to hardwood trees.
        It is known to attack and kill healthy maple trees, as well as poplar, willow, elm,
        birch, ash, and horse chestnut. Suspect insects need to be reported.</string>

    <string name="emerald_ash_borer">Emerald Ash Borer: An invasive species that attracts only ash trees.  This insect
        has the potential to devastate the ash population in our forests as well as our
        landscapes.  Suspect insects need to be reported.</string>

    <string name="japanese_beetle">Japanese Beetle: Grubs feed on the roots of lawns, leaving dead patches.  The adult
        feed on a wide variety of plants, leaving the leaves skeletonized.</string>

    <string name="tomato_hornworm">Tomato Hornworm: This caterpillar can reach 3 to 4 inches at maturity and feeds on
        tomato, eggplant, pepper, and potato plants.  The adult moth is the sphinx moth,
        sometimes called the hummingbird moth, and can have a wingspan of 4 to 5 inches.</string>

    <string name="cabbageworm">Cabbageworm: This caterpillar can completely defoliate plants and can eat their way
        into a head of cabbage.  The adult moth is white with several black markings on its
        wings.</string>

    <string name="colorado_potato_beetle">Colorado Potato Beetle: The adults and larvae feed on the foliage of potatoes,
        eggplant, tomatoes, and peppers.  Adult beetles overwinter in the soil.</string>

    <string name="lily_leaf_beetle">Lily Leaf Beetle: The larvae and adult beetles feed on the leaves and flower buds of
        lilies that grow from buds, quickly devastating the plants.  Daylilies are not
        affected.</string>

    <string name="lacewing">Lacewing: Lacewings are beneficial insects.  The larvae are predators of aphids,
        mealybugs, and insect eggs.  The adult feeds on pollen and insects.</string>

    <string name="ground_beetle">Ground Beetle: Ground beetles are beneficial insects that feed on serious lawn and
        garden pests including cutworms, armyworms, and mole crickets.  Both the adults and
        larvae are predatory.</string>

    <string name="housefly">Housefly: Annoying pest indoors and out.  Proper sanitation, including removal of
        food sources, can reduce breeding.  Window screens are effective in keeping the
        flies out.  Once inside, a flyswatter is the least expensive control option.</string>

    <string name="boxelderbug">Boxelderbug: An outdoor pest of boxelder trees. A nuisance pest around the home,
        usually in the fall as they seek  sheltered sites for overwintering.  Can occur in
        large numbers.  </string>


</resources>
